const STORE = [
    {
      question: 'What position on the Gryffindor Quidditch team did Oliver Wood play?',
      answers: [
        'Keeper',
        'Chaser',
        'Beater',
        'Seeker'
        ],
      correctAnswer: 'Keeper',
    },
    {
      question: 'Which of the Deathly Hallows does Harry receive as a Christmas gift?',
      answers: [
        'Elder Wand',
        'Cloak of Invisibility',
        'Resurrection Stone',
        'Golden Snitch'
        ],
        correctAnswer: 'Cloak of Invisibility',
    },
    {
      question: 'Which of the following is NOT a protection for the Philosopher’s (Sorcerer’s) Stone?',
      answers: [
        'Mirror of Erised',
        'Cornish Pixies',
        'Devil’s Snare',
        'Wizard’s Chess'
        ],
        correctAnswer: 'Cornish Pixies',
    },
    {
      question: 'Who destroys a horcrux first?',
      answers: [
        'Neville Longbottom',
        'Albus Dumbledore',
        'Harry Potter',
        'Hermione Granger'
        ],
      correctAnswer: 'Harry Potter',
    },
    {
      question: 'Who was NOT a member of the ‘Slug Club’?',
      answers: [
        'Hermione Granger',
        'Harry Potter',
        'Ron Weasley',
        'Cormac McLaggen'
        ],
      correctAnswer: 'Ron Weasley',
    },
    {
      question: 'Who does Harry accidentally ‘blow up,’ causing him to run away from Privet Drive?',
      answers: [
        'Vernon Dursley',
        'Marge Dursley',
        'Dudley Dursley',
        'Petunia Dursley'
        ],
      correctAnswer: 'Marge Dursley',
    },
    {
      question: 'What is NOT a magical means of transportation?',
      answers: [
      'Floo Powder',
      'Gambol and Japes',
      'Knight Bus',
      'Portkey'
      ],
      correctAnswer: 'Gambol and Japes',
    },
    {
      question: 'Which ghost teaches History of Magic at Hogwarts?',
      answers: [
        'Myrtle Warren',
        'Helena Ravenclaw',
        'Cuthbert Binns',
        'Sir Nicholas de Mimsy-Porpington'
      ],
      correctAnswer: 'Cuthbert Binns',
    },
    {
      question: 'Which of the following dragons was NOT used in the Triwizard tournament?',
      answers: [
      'Swedish Short-Snout',
      'Chinese Fireball',
      'Hungarian Horntail',
      'Norwegian Ridgeback'
      ],
      correctAnswer: 'Norwegian Ridgeback',
    },
    {
      question: 'Which is NOT a shop in Diagon Alley?',
      answers: [
        'Honeydukes',
        'Flourish & Blott’s',
        'Madam Malkin’s Robes for All Occasions',
        'Eeylops Owl Emporium'
    ],
    correctAnswer: 'Honeydukes',
    }
];
